Come on.
>> We have the LA photos.
>> Every equipment size.
>> What's up, Bolt fam?
>> Signed, done.
>> Just put the pen to the paper.
>> Gratefully part of the Bolt fam. Ready
to get to work.
>> We are closing in on free agency. Here
we go. When we go through free agency,
we get a list of names of players that
the coaches and scouts want to see. We
will make an all plays and the key plays
cut up for them. I bring this in. We'll
name it alphabetically so it sorts in
the right order. put in that folder for
that specific position so the coaches
know where to go and immediately are
able to access that video.
>> Essentially, you always got to start
with the flight in. So, my itineraries
are always going to look like, okay,
here's the guy. He's arriving at, let's
say, 8:30 at night on a Sunday. We're
probably going to bring him into the
facility on Monday. And then with every
single player that we bring in, I make
sure we have a host for him. So, I
always have a go-to person that's always
there for him. We're going to start with
some doctor's appointments in the
morning and then he's going to come back
to the facility. He's going to meet his
coaches.
>> Uh, one thing that we always do for free
agency is wait for the players to arrive
so we can capture their first moments
walking into the pool and then also
saying their name on the big screen
behind us.
>> He's going to go through kind of that
lap of, you know, meeting with your
position coach. You're going to meet
with your coordinator and then they meet
with coach Harbaugh.
We usually walk them around the
building, show them around, whether it
be the weight room so they can meet Ben
Herbert who's awesome. They can meet Sal
and Marco down in athletic training. And
of course, got to go see equipment as
well.
>> So, when we sign a new player for free
agency, the uh previous team they were
on, their equipment staff will send us
kind of a sheet like this. And this
basically gives us every equipment
sizing related to them. So, just to get
them started, we'll kind of give them
some workout gear, head to toe, shirts,
shorts, uh, training pants, socks,
slide, shoes, all that kind of basic
stuff. So, we'll just kind of fill him
in this empty locker. Put his laundry
loop on the hook.
Then we'll have a full zip hoodie,
couple long sleeves,
couple short sleeves,
sweatpants, and then some training pants
and some extra hangers. Some shoes. So,
we'll put those in the the pull out
drawer. So, we got his training shoes,
shower slides, got some socks,
compression shorts, and then practice
shorts. We just got to lay it out so he
has a feel for everything. That's kind
of the the general spread for everything
we get the free agents.
>> They'll go sign uh then we go do some
really fun media.
So every agent comes in, they sign their
contract, we do a photo with them just
to kind of start their Chargers journey
or when they resign like Josh Harris
today, we do it just so through the
years we can see their progression. This
is our podcast table which you if you've
ever watched Chargers weekly, you see
prominently. It's also a giant
reflective surface though, so we turn it
sideways. That way we can get a
reflection on the board and make a cool
looking photo. Let me turn over that
one. So, for each one, we'll tether the
camera into the laptop, bring it right
into Lightroom. That way, we can get it
edited up real quick, crop it, send it
out to social so they can get it posted
for you. We do different tiny mics. We
kind of like pick at their interests and
pull out different things that we think
that they might like to do so that we
play into their personality a little
bit. And we shoot several things with
them so that we can kind of bank those
for the off season. We capture their
arrivals, selfie video to the fans, and
just kind of get a real glimpse into
like what goes on in their first day.
>> Once photos finished with their contract
signing photos and social's done their
thing, we'll go ahead and move this desk
out of the way. It's on wheels, so it
makes it easy.
So, we have this hype set behind us. So,
when we bring in new players, we want to
shoot some hero images, hero shots to
use in our highlights and future use. We
have this crazy motion graphic showing
all of our brand colors and logos. And
while we're shooting, we have this nifty
little monitor here which connects to
our camera. While the camera op is
getting shots, we can have a director
looking through our monitor here and
directing to get the shots that we need.
Typically we have two cameras and we are
shooting simultaneously so that we cut
them together in a dynamic way for our
highlights.
>> After the free agents finish with their
photos, social the hype set, they come
over to the feature set. We try to do
more of a personality based piece with
the free agents so that fans can really
get to know our new guys. The goal is to
have a compilation piece that splices
each of the guys together that came in
for content. We have two cameras, we
have a monitor set up, and then we have
somebody producing. The player will come
in, throw the mic on them real quick,
they'll sit down, and we just have a
stack of questions for them that they
can go through.
>> Myth busting, and I start crying every
potential place we were going to. So,
>> to start, we have three separate colors
to go uh up on our socials and on our
digital platforms. Uh we wanted to make
sure that we had as much variety as
possible. you could have multiple
players get announced at a certain time.
So you don't want to be posting the same
graphic over and over and over again. So
we did a powder background one, what we
call sand, which is a white color
background, and then we did our gold so
that we have options for these. We have
the LA photos lined up in the background
to kind of give a vibe of different
areas in LA. But for Resign guys, since
we have so many photos of them in our
jersey, I wanted to make sure that we
showcase as many photos of the guys as
we possibly can.
>> This right here is behind the app. We're
going to make a change for Denzel
Perryman since we're signing him back.
So once I find him, I have to change his
type from unrestricted free agent to a
not selected and from pending to either
extended, agreed to terms, and he can
move to extended, he can move to
tendered, he can move to signed. That's
how we set up the app part of this.
>> Once we sign a player, our job is to
make sure that they have a profile set
up and ready to rock and roll. We just
make sure that like all their
information's in. We set a universal
password for these guys. That way,
they're kind of able to use it on their
tablet and access the film super easily.
After that, I go ahead and make sure I
assign it to their position group. That
way, their coach can kind of go ahead,
put all the information in, and they can
access it during meetings or at home
when they're kind of going back and
forth. I'll update it. It'll show up in
our system, and they're ready to rock
and roll. Once uh we make the profiles
like on Thundercloud uh we all give them
their personalized tablet. So we have
this app called the Catapult
ThunderCloud and we just log them in
with their credentials and with this app
they'll be able to see all the video and
their playbook.
>> Yeah. Did you see what I wrote?
>> It's really great. We get to bring in
families. The family is the support
system behind the players
for the support here. This is such a
great place. It's such a great facility.
It's really nice to show it off to
people who get to see it for the first
time.
>> This is such a big collaborative effort
between so many different departments.
There's a lot of group chats, a lot of
phone calls. Everyone's trying to stay
on top of everything, keep communication
clear. It's really about showing these
guys how great the city of LA is and how
great all the people are here.
>> Got to go with five. That's the next
round number we got.
>> All right. Uh it's time to come fight.
>> Excited for day one on the wall and
everything. Let's go.